Leo Huettel

Leo Huettel

103 E Chester St. APT B Lafayette, CO 80026

303-319-8918 lehu9098@colorado.edu https://www.linkedin.com/in/leo-huettel-35197073/

Skills

<u>Proficient</u>
Vue Js, Javascript, HTML, CSS, C++, SQL, Firebase, Vuetify

Familiar(Used, but not extensively) MongoDB, Python, Github, linux, Angular, Node JS, Scala, bootstrap, slack, trello, npm, JQuery My name is Leo Huettel and I am a 23 year old working towards my BA in computer Science from the University of Colorado, Boulder. Over the course of my college career I have been searching for an area of computer science that allows for me to be creative, innovative, and help others have an easier time using technology. This past year I took a software development class and fell in love with web design and development. I am looking for a company where I can grow my software development skills while balancing my love for the outdoors. In the future, my goal is to become a full stack software developer with the skills and tools to create whatever my imagination brews up. Past that, I could see myself working into more of a management role so I can utilize my extraverted, outgoing personality as well as my leadership skills that I have honed while leading guided fishing trips for Rocky Mountain Anglers.

Experience

Rocky Mountain Anglers/ Web Developer

March 2020 - Current, Boulder, CO

<u>Project Description:</u> Rocky Mountain Anglers Website is outdated. In March of this year, I pitched to the Owner, Randy Hicks, the possibility of developing him a new website. Since I have been in the Fly Fishing Industry for the last 4 years as a guide and a part time shop employee I realized and understood, better than most, what important details needed to be readily available to our users as well as what the shop staff needed to easily update and modify the contents of the site. Unfortunately, with the situation of COVID-19, Rocky Mountain Anglers was closed and there was a long delay in the project due to a lack of access to company photos and information I needed. With that being said, I am on track to have the site completely finished by the end of October 2020.

<u>Technology Used:</u> Vue Js, Node Js, Firebase, Vuetify, Javascript, Css, Html Link: https://rocky-mt.web.app/

Software Development Project/ Bonsai Buddy

January 2019 - May 2019 / Boulder, Colorado

August 2016 - Present

<u>Statement of Purpose</u>: Bonsai trees and plants in general require a lot of attention. From personal experience I know it's extremely easy to forget to water your plants or find someone to water your plants when you leave the house for a couple days. Our app Bon-sai Buddies purpose is to allow plant owners to

carefully maintain their plants through an automated watering process, as well as watch their plants remotely to ensure they are as healthy as can be.

Responsibilities: In this project I was responsible for working on the front end designing the layout of our website, helping integrate our database, as well as helping build the database for storing user login information.

Skills Developed: Learned Agile development techniques, Project Management Skills, Time Management Skills, Leadership Skills, Communication Skills.

Technology Used: Github, HTML, CSS, PostgreSQL, Javascript, Heroku

Rocky Mountain Anglers/fly fishing guide

May 2017 - Current, Boulder, CO

Job Description: Led Guided fishing trips for clients from all over the world, teaching and interacting with them to provide the best outdoor experience possible. Responsibilities include looking out for the wellbeing and safety of each client, making each client feel respected and comfort- able, and designing a trip plan that accommodates all clients specific needs.

Education

University of Colorado at Boulder / BA in Computer Science

August 2016 - December 2020, Boulder, Co

GPA: Cumulative - 3.51 GPA: technical - 3.63